// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "When is the Army Day celebrated in India every year?",
    answer: "January 15",
    options: [
      "January 15",
      "January 10",
      "January 12",
      "December 4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Why January 15 is Celebrated as the Army Day in India?",
    answer: "Field Marshal K.M. Cariaapa took over as the first Inian Commander-in-Chief of the Indian Army",
    options: [
      "India won the war against Pakistan",
      "Birth anniversary of Field Marshal K.M. Cariappa",
      "Indian Rebellion of 1857 began on this day",
      "Field Marshal K.M. Cariaapa took over as the first Inian Commander-in-Chief of the Indian Army"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is the highest rank of the Indian Army?",
    answer: "Field Marshal",
    options: [
      "Brigadier",
      "General",
      "Field Marshal",
      "Major"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "When was the first war between ndi and Pakistan took place?",
    answer: "1947",
    options: [
      "1947",
      "1965",
      "1999",
      "2005"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who was the last British Commander-in-Chief of the Indian Army?",
    answer: "General Francis  Butcher",
    options: [
      "General Rob Lockhart",
      "General Francis  Butcher",
      "General Frank Messervy",
      "General Alan Hartley"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "When was the Indian Army founded?",
    answer: "1 April 1895",
    options: [
      "15 August 1947",
      "26 January 1950",
      "1 April 1895",
      "15 January 1857"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who was the first Field Marshal the Indian Army?",
    answer: "Sam Manekshaw",
    options: [
      "Nirmal Chandra Vij",
      "Arjan Singh",
      "Kodandera M. Cariappa",
      "Sam Manekshaw"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the smallest unit of the Indian Army called?",
    answer: "Section",
    options: [
      "Platoon",
      "Section",
      "Battery",
      "Battalion"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The PIN code of the Army Post Office starts with?",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "1",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who was the first recipient of the Param Vir Chakra?",
    answer: "Major Somnath Sharma",
    options: [
      "Major Dhan Singh Thapa",
      "Major Shaitan Singh",
      "Major Somnath Sharma",
      "Major Hoshiar Singh"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];